rajrang.com 2012-02-11

# Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) We are committed to protecting your privacy and encourage you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we protect the information you disclose to us. If you believe that [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) is not abiding by our posted privacy policy, please e-mail us at [customercare@rajrang.com](mailto:customercare@rajrang.com) Information Collection and Use 

[Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

My Account

When you make your first purchase on our site, you will be asked to create an account. By creating an account, the system will remember your personal and purchase information and the checkout process on future purchases will be fast, easy and secure. Creating an account is also fast and easy: simply enter your personal information once and select your very own username and password. Then during checkout on your next purchase, just login and the system will take care of the rest. At all times, your personal information is accessible to you to review, edit, or update as necessary by clicking on the "My Account" link.

Order

We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and financial information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to communicate with the customer.

Internal Use

We may compare and review your personally identifiable information for errors, omissions and accuracy. We may also use your personally identifiable information internally to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, Web Site content and product offerings. Your personally identifiable information may also be used internally to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, behavior and generally to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Web Site and our marketing programs.

Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection: We may collect and disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may collect and possibly share personally identifiable information and any other information available to us in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any personal or as otherwise required by law. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.

Refer a Friend

Using a form available at Rajrang, you can also refer a friend to the Rajrang Web Site. You and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested to ensure that your friend will know that you have requested that Rajrang send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted.

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the web site that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer.

Sharing

We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from users of the site to a third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of the assets or stock relating to [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/). Finally, notwithstanding any other provision of this privacy policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we believe that we are required to do so (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (iii) to enforce our Terms of Service; (iv) to protect our operations or those of any affiliated entities; (v) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/), any affiliated entities, you or others; and (vi) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/)

Catalog, Newsletters, Etc.

If a user wishes to subscribe to our catalog, newsletter, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and e-mail address to provide these communications. Because we respect our users' privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below. On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an e-mail. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

Surveys & Sweepstakes

From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, shipping address and e-mail address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Special Events: If you choose to participate in a special event (for example, a promotion, contest or sweepstake), [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) may share your personally identifiable information with those organizations participating in the applicable event. Typically, these third parties do not use your information for any other purpose other than to manage the event. In some cases these third-party partners may send you promotional materials regarding their products and services. In these cases, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out, and not have your personally identifiable information shared with that third-party partner.

If at any time you choose to enter a [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) feedback contest and allow us to post your feedback on our Web Site, we will remove your feedback from our Web Site at any time if you send your request via e-mail to [customercare@rajrang.com](mailto:customercare@rajrang.com) Send this Product to a Friend: When you e-mail a product to a friend, you and your friend's names and e-mail addresses are requested. This ensures that your friend will know that you have requested that [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) send them an e-mail. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted.

Security

[Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) encryption software. While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. In addition, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access.

Your Concent to Gemcojewels.com Privacy Policy

By using this Web Site, you agree to [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) privacy policy. This is our entire and exclusive privacy policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may occasionally update this privacy policy. When a revision is made we will revise the "last updated" date on this page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to stay informed about how we are protecting your information. Your continued use of this Web Site constitutes your consent to this privacy policy and any updates.

For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of our Web Site, please see our Rajrang Product policies and Legal Notices.

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact the [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) service department at [customercare@rajrang.com](mailto:customercare@rajrang.com). You may also send us your comments about the [Rajrang.com](http://www.rajrang.com/) Site or the shopping experience in general, as we always appreciate feedback.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, send us an e-mail at [customercare@rajrang.com](mailto:customercare@rajrang.com) for more information.
